Hi everybody, it's Mike again with UGtastic.
It is the night before SCNA and I've been getting everything prepared, ready to go
and got my microphone and camera set up and I have my workflow down
for the day and I also went through and I've caught up on some tasks
and there's quite a few people that I owe packages of stickers.
I have, let's see, a bunch of stickers
that I'm going to be sending out over the next few days as soon as I can get to the post office
but I want to thank everybody who's taken the time to
get back with me. The Brighton PHP group, let's see, that was
Rich Sage from the Brighton PHP group
and then James Sitcom from the
PHP Hampshire group and people who have been following
and just generally supporting the page through
likes and tweets and retweets and posts and blog posts
I've got Ivan Pierre who's been really liking us
a lot, LinkedIn and Marcus Tacker who
he a while ago created a series of
presentations that he did over in Germany about
their user community and their technical communities and
utilized kind of the style of the UGtastic iHeart user group
so that was really cool so I have some stickers for him and
like I mentioned, Rich Sage and Kyle Toll
I really appreciate the support but I have a whole bunch more
packages of stickers so if you go and you create some
content or retweet or blog post or
generally help promote UGtastic
I will be eternally grateful and
if it's in the next couple of days I'll be able to send you
a packet of stickers, there's a variety of stickers from different companies
some Ruby, some .NET, some Git, there's a few
consulting companies and some UGtastic stickers too of course
and some different conferences that I've been to over the years
so thank you again for everybody who's supported
and for those of you who are going to be at SCNA tomorrow, I'm looking forward to interviewing
you and I really appreciate all the support and I'm looking forward to even more
conversations. Thanks, bye!